https://www.buildingdesign.co.uk/privacy.htm

Mechanical / HVAC - Services
Data Centres - Design / Maint.
Hospitals - Design / Maintenance
Facilities - Interiors / Maint.
Privacy Policy
As you may be aware, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) came into effect May
25th 2018.
As a consequence of this, we are required to provide you with information on how
we handle personal information about you and how to contact us, and if you have any questions about our data processing or wish to change your preferences with regard to that processing or the ways in which we contact you.
You may request further details about our processing activities, including a complete record of the data we store about you, ask us to correct the information we hold, or ask us to stop processing it, by writing to us at Arundel Jones Associates, Unit 1C, Hill Farm Business Park, Linton Hill, Maidstone, Kent ME17 4AL or emailing us on admin@buildingdesign.co.uk (Tel: 01622 745333)
You can change your contact preferences at any time by writing to or emailing us on the addresses above. You may also ask us to delete the information we hold about you.
We may contact you by post, email or telephone (including SMS messages), where we have the relevant contact information, unless you have previously specified preferences in this regard.
We do not, and will never, share your information with any third parties except where we are compelled to by law or where you have given express permission
to do so.
Featured Companies on the BuildingDesign Portal
If you have requested information or direct marketing from any of the companies featured on BuildingDesign and later wish to withdraw
or change your consent, please contact the relevant company direct from which you have received marketing so that they can unsubscribe you from their lists.
The full list of Companies can be found here »
BuildingDesign e-Newsletter
If you have subscribed to our twice weekly e-Newsletter and no
longer wish to receive it, you can unsubscribe at any time, by
emailing
news@buildingdesign.co.uk. When requesting removal via email, please send your email to us using the email account that is subscribed to the mailing list.
If you change your mind at any time, you can add your email address to the Newsletter distribution list visiting our Newsletter Subscribe
page
Data Breaches
We will report any unlawful data breach of this website’s database or the database(s) of any of our third party data processors to any and all relevant persons and authorities within 72 hours of the breach if it is apparent that personal data stored in an identifiable manner has been stolen.
Data Controller
The data controller of this website is: Arundel Jones Associates, Unit 1C, Hill Farm Business Park, Linton Hill, Maidstone, Kent ME17 4AL
Registered in England & Wales No. 07737227
Cookies
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors. We
website.
By using
our
website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.
Collecting personal information
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:
Information about your computer - (Type: PC/Mac/Mobile Device and Operating System)
Your visits to and use of this website including geographical location
Web Browser type and version
Referral
source,
length
of
visit, page views and website navigation paths.
Cookie Policy »
Terms of Use »
©
BuildingDesign Media
- Hill Farm Business Park, Linton Hill, Maidstone, Kent, ME17 4AL, Tel: 01622 745333 - Reg No. 07737227
|
BuildingDesign Media is a trading name of Arundel Jones Associates Ltd
